<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on elsos site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on elsos site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 12:29:40 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Woman Called Fujiko Mine Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/woman-called-fujiko-mine-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 12:29:40 +0300</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/woman-called-fujiko-mine-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Very very unique anime. First the artstyle is really good, rather &amp;ldquo;sketchy&amp;rdquo; feeling, and I love it. There&amp;rsquo;s an interesting thing where this anime uses what feels like loading screens for transitions, very odd thing that I don&amp;rsquo;t hate. Music is mostly good but the OP just sucks. ED is good enough. But the shining part of this anime is the storyline and characters.  This anime has such an excellent portrayal of female sexuality, one of the few times where it feels like she completely owns it and uses it to control people. This isn&amp;rsquo;t that rare in anime, but the kicker that makes this feel so different is the lack of comedy surrounding it. There&amp;rsquo;s some heavy subjects that women are unfortunately subject to and they&amp;rsquo;re handled good here. This is also a Lupin anime and the way it integrates wider Lupin characters while also being a Fujiko Mine story first is very good.&#xA;Only real downside I have(other than the OP) is that the last episode goes overboard with non-sensical plot twists. Which sucks because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t detract that much, and these twists aren&amp;rsquo;t &lt;em&gt;bad&lt;/em&gt; but it&amp;rsquo;s still a downside that you&amp;rsquo;ll probably realize when watching it. But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t change my opinion that this anime is one word. Tasteful&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
